It's hard to believe.
Chun-bin is a father.
Feels like he was a rookie just yesterday.
Don't remind me.
He was so impulsive after the academy.
Nothing could stop him.
Chun-bin, we're really grateful to you for keeping his head on straight.
Well, it's nice of you to say so.
But I wasn't much of a mentor.
At least not after I quit.
That's in the past.
I heard that you're a big-shot lawyer now.
If you ask me, you're better off.
Trust me, you look much better in a suit.
I would have loved for Chun-bin to follow after you,
but that man is police through and through.
That he is, more than I was.
Fair.
Now, I'm sure you didn't stop by to see me.
Let me give him a call.
He hasn't been home for a few days.
This case he's on has been running him ragged.
Really?
I'd blame his partner.
Xiaoli always ends up with the tough cases.
Do me a favor.
Answer that for me.
Hey, it's me.
Are you coming home tonight?
Our daughter has been missing her father,
and Captain Qian stopped by to see you.
It's fine.
We're not in a hurry.
Promise me you'll get some sleep.
Love you.
Well, he's not coming.
Sorry about that.
Can't say I'm surprised, though.
He's barely been at home since I got pregnant.
That's the job.
Which is why I went into business for myself.
Curious, has he been working on the Chuita Games case recently?
I wouldn't know.
He never tells me anything about his work.
And that's fine by me.
I just worry.
It's bad for the baby.
The first thing I taught him was how to keep his mouth shut.
I'm glad to see that at least one lesson's stuck.
So, you're having a girl?
Maybe.
Nowadays, doctors can't say.
Chun-Bin wants a daughter, though.
So he's been buying stuff like this, despite not knowing.
You know what he said?
His faith will change fate.
It's that strong.
Can you believe that, man?
He told me the same thing years ago.
Oh, right.
I brought you a box of fruit.
Ma, please bring it to the kitchen.
Uh, you don't have to carry that heavy thing around.
I'll just have Beam do it later.
I insist.
Please, sit.
You can put your dirty clothes in this bag after you're done changing, okay?
What's with the stuffed animal?
Not for me, I guess.
Uh, I completely forgot about that.
Grabbed it while I was getting your clothes.
It was so cute, I had to buy it.
I'm just learning all kinds of things about you today.
It's for my daughter, wise guy.
Now go get changed.
I'm sorry.
I feel bad that you came all this way for nothing.
I was in the area.
I'll warn you before showing up next time.
Now go relax.
Get some rest.
I will.
Goodbye.
I really hope I'm not coming down with a cold.
I don't want to be pregnant and sick while my husband can't take care of me.
That was some amazing acting back there, boss.
If I didn't know any better, I'd have thought you were here to see an old friend.
Don't you ever burp like that around me again, or I will cut out your throat.
Did you get it?
Yeah.
I snagged one of the ones by the front door when I moved the apples to the kitchen.
Sorry I missed you.
I'm still busy.
Take a rain check?
That's fine.
This case must be tricky.
Think you'll be done soon?
Hard to say.
I'm hoping we can wrap this up quick.
I wouldn't want to miss the big day.
Yes, that would be a shame.
Fine.
I'll try again sometime.
Till then.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
All right.
How's it fit?
Here.
It's hard to strangle yourself to death.
Your muscles would give out before you died.
We don't know how he did it, but you mean dislocated his cricoid cartilage.
Crushed his windpipe.
Huh?
If that's true, why did the officer still lie to me?
I didn't give you the details because you told me that you already knew.
Or I thought you did.
I asked you if you were filled in, remember?
How would I know that's what you meant?
Maybe try being a bit more direct next time.
That guy keeping secrets, but that was way too vague.
How are you?
Huh?
I know everything that happened.
I was the one who stabbed Lu Guang.
We went over it all, and we have a theory.
If this guy does have the power to control people, Liu Min didn't kill himself.
He was used in the same way Chao Ling was.
There are too many questions.
Who is this guy?
Who's he using?
How does he do it?
He'll find out that Lu Guang survived.
And he'll come for him when he does.
We need to be prepared.
Until we know more, we need any advantage we can get.
This ward is one of them.
Had to get special permission to use it.
This building is brand new and hasn't officially been put into use.
That means no wandering staff or patients to worry about.
Right now, we're the only ones who know Lu Guang is here.
The building also has top-of-the-line surveillance.
I made you all accounts on the hospital's network so you can access the feed.
Download the app and stay here.
Keep an eye on things.
We'll be on standby.
Anyone shows up, we'll know it's them.
Remember, Lu Guang's not here.
Thanks to Chao Ling, you're visiting a family friend.
A family friend?
As in...
We have no idea who this killer is.
I had to find someone we could trust who wasn't very close to us.
So I asked Master Suwen if he'd bring his father-in-law in for surgery.
You did what?
Excuse me, he's still recovering.
You're the family?
Yes, ma'am, we are.
Good.
I can go for his post-op care with you.
I'm assuming you're both his parents?
Not quite.
He's my father, actually.
Wait, white hair but flawless skin?
This man looks young enough to pass for your grandchild.
What is his secret?
This and that.
Doing tai chi, climbing stairs, those kinds of things.
That's all?
I guess it's true that life is in the movement.
I mean, I would believe it too if I didn't know better.
Just shut up.
Thank you both for everything you've done for us.
We appreciate it.
This could be nothing, but the killer may have slipped up when we were fighting.
It was what he said to me.
I can't let it go.
I think his power's like mine.
Wait!
No!
I can't believe it's been right in front of me.
You covered that dark room with photos.
Because you need them as well.
It didn't make any sense.
Why would he make that connection?
No one would assume photos could be used that way, unless they'd done it.
If that's the case, then his power most likely relies on photos in the same way that ours do.
Or something similar.
That's not all he told me.
Although I don't know how true any of it was.
You're teleporting with pictures?
What a convenient power.
I think I might take it and see what kind of trouble I can get into.
As far as I know, our powers can't be taken.
But with how confident he was, I'm starting to think that I could be very wrong.
Hey, this ringing any bells for you?
I'm not quite sure.
That's all I got.
And it's not like I can prove it.
But just for safety, I deleted everything we put online.
All our personal stuff, plus anything relating to the photo studio.
Which wasn't much, since Liu Guang and I don't post a lot.
And he's already a ghost.
He doesn't even have social media.
Some might say that he doesn't exist.
At least I exist enough to delete those stupid photos you made me take.
But I don't post a lot.
How was he able to find something to control me with?
When he killed Liu Min, he took the only connection we had to him.
This is all we've got now.
Can you check the recent photos?
Chunbin, did you bring the phone like I asked?
Given what we know, we think Liu Min was familiar with the killer.
We searched his phone and chat records, but didn't find anything.
It turned out to be a dead end.
For us, not you.
Can you find something that we couldn't?
Sure. I'll try.
Our IT department was able to crack Liu Min's password.
Start with the most recent photos and see what you can learn with that power of yours.
Lu Guang, you're still healing.
Be careful.
Yeah, don't push yourself.
Huh?
Hey, that's Officer Chen's phone.
Chenbin?
Damn it!
Hang on, I'm coming with you!
Actually, it might be better if I stay.
Hey, Captain Xiao.
Did you find him?
Not yet.
It's like he vanished.
Did you notice anything strange when he picked you up?
By the way, I picked you up a change of clothes.
So, hey, did they fill you in on the whole situation?
Do me a favor, answer that for me.
I might not make it home.
I'm still on a case.
Promise you'll get some sleep.
Done.
Love you.
If that's the case, then his power most likely relies on photos in the same way that ours do.
Or something similar.
Did the killer take control of him?
Did Chenbin put this picture away?
I guess he wants to use one of the baby.
Even if he's being controlled, he should have left to the main exit.
I would have seen him by now.
Look how happy your dad is.
And soon, he can meet you in person.
Oh, no.
Chenbin!
Hey!
Don't you dare!
Come on!
Tung!
Breathe, damn it!
Hey, what's going on?
Captain Xiao, are you still there?
Hello?
Hey!
I've got the surveillance footage on your phone.
Oh, right.
Good thinking.
No, it's him.
But how could Officer Chen fall off the building?
I can't love.
Someone's coming down from the roof.
What?
I'll go after him.
The building only has two exits.
Cut him off.
Okay.
I'm going with you.
No!
Stay here.
Help Lu Guang.
What the hell was that for Xiaoling?
Listen, idiot.
I appreciate you trying to protect me, but I don't need it.
What I need is your trust!
Get to the first floor.
That way, you can cover both exits.
What about you?
I'll be fine.
I can lock myself in the room.
Quit stalling.
Don't let that bastard escape.
I just called it in.
Police are 15 minutes away.
Where's Xiaol?
We'll have more time to worry about the Captain after we've dealt with the man from the roof.
You're right.
You should see an emergency exit.
That will give you a straight shot to the first floor so you can cut him off.
Yeah.
Damn it.
Where'd he go?
I'm wasting time scrolling through camera feeds.
I need a better picture.
Stop right there.
Hey, what are you doing here, Missy?
You startled me.
Give Lyumian's phone to me.
The police will be here soon.
Just give up.
It's all my fault.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
It's all over now, man.
They won't stop until they put a bullet in my head.
What am I going to do?
I don't want to die.
They don't want to die.
Wait.
First, I'll kill you.
Look out.
Never interrupt me.
This guy's no joke.
Is he the street fighter Master Seawin talked about?
No.
Jennifer.
Let's go.
Oh.
well
.
You're dead meat, buddy.
No way!
That's in time.
You find Liu An's phone?
I'm not seeing it.
Officer Chen might still have it.
Don't bother!
Her backup's almost here!
Well, that's funny.
Mine just arrived.
Do what you want with the guy.
Leave the girl.
She's all mine now.
Hey, talk to me.
What's going on?
Did you get the phone?
No.
You